[{"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Do you think that you were acting legally?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "In what you were doing?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, it was my stuff.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "And why is that?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "It definitely is going to be two words, \"not guilty.\"", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "So when the judge at the arraignment says, how do you plead to kidnapping, how do you plead to rape and whatever else, what are you going to say?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "And, again, that begs the question, well, what kind of circumstances could possibly justify all that, showing that you love your daughter?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "And in terms of where this is going to go, it's going to come down, presumably, to his word against his former attorney's word, right?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "That if they didn't give me the stuff, you have to call the police.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Well, what was his advice to you regarding the entire plan?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Not until the police came.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Did you have any understanding whether you could detain people or not?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "You can demand your property?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Well, are you having any alcohol?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I had a joke that my doctor says I should never have an empty glass is what I would tell the waitress.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "And how much were you drinking, if you can remember?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, he's not a bad witness.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What do you make of seeing him finally give evidence?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Is that likely?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "LORIA ALLRED, CIVIL RIGHTS ATTORNEY: Well, I mean, first of all, I think that's insulting to the judge who is the one who sentenced him.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Would you agree with all that, Gloria?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I was shocked.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Tell me this, I mean, talking of behavior involving attorneys, I was pretty shocked by the tone that Ariel Castro's attorneys -- were you shocked?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Exceptional cruelty is what they found or special cruelty.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Should she should be?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "It's looking -- if the jury goes this stage of saying, yes, we do think she is eligible for it, aren't they more likely to say we think she should have it?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "I like that.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Well, if you think that the IRS commissioner should be fired, do you think that the president of the United States, George W. Bush, should have been fired for acting on faulty intelligence and sending troops to -- the Iraq War?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Similar question.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "And Alan?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "These are great questions.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "How do we make sure the IRS is taken out of politics?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "You ask the money question.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Why has he had had to go, when from what I hear, he wasn't actually running the IRS when all this went one?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, it's going further than it would have a couple of days ago.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Where is that going?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Absolutely agree.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Dana?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Excellent.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Well, one is bad.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "When you look at these three scandals in totality, are they real scandals or are they run of the mill issues that any White House has to deal with?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "UMSFELD: I think the way to think of it is that, as I think Mark Twain said, trust leaves on horseback and returns on foot.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Do you believe that, given all of the e-mails that have come out today?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, I would count them as kind of as undecided.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "No, I'm saying that what's happened is there have been different stories coming out.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Are you suggesting that people, either Hillary Clinton or President Obama, have lied about this?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Otherwise it's supposition, isn't it?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I've been in and out of government since 1962, when I was elected to Congress.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Can that ever be justified under the First Amendment, never mind anything else?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "UMSFELD: I said -- one of my rules is, if you don't know, say you don't know.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "So it's wrong?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Or, as I suspect, is the potential person who leaked it so important and so high up the food chain, they've got to find out who it was.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Is there something so bad that it might cause government to do something like that?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Because I like to grill people on it.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Why do you call this the Grill?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Was he right, the president, to fire the acting chief of the IRS?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I think some people may end up going to jail.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Should there be more heads rolling?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Do we know enough yet?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "UMSFELD: Oh, I have no idea about that.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Should Eric Holder consider his position, do you think?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "UMSFELD: I think that the currency a president or leader has is trust.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "If it turns out that the president has lied about Benghazi, or about the IRS, for example, if it turns out senior White House officials knew more than they're saying about what was going on and the original idea to target the Tea Party came from then -- these are pure hypotheticals, how serious would that be?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Well, her father told me that.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "What did you make of the Rumsfeld rule that Joyce gave us there?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "That I felt that way?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Well, sure, I've argued with presidents, I've argued with people.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Can you share one with me?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "You know, of course you do.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Do you have any regrets about the way Iraq is today?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Oh, you bet your life.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Are they?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Well, I thought about that coming over here.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "In \"Rumsfeld's Rules,\" what rule would you have for me?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130515pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 694}]